Coinbase Global Privacy Policy

Last Updated: November 20, 2025_._ Previous Privacy Policy can be found [here](https://www.coinbase.com/legal/privacy-old).

* * *

We at Coinbase (the Coinbase entities listed in [Section 12 below](#our-relationship-with-you), referred to here as “**we**”, “**us**” or “**our**”) respect and protect the privacy of those who explore our Services (“**Users**”) and Users who sign up for and access our Services (“**Customers**”) (together referred throughout this policy as “**you**” and “**your**”).

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, and share personal information when you explore, sign up for or access our **“Services”**, which include the services offered on our websites, including [coinbase.com](https://www.coinbase.com/), [coinbase.com/exchange](https://www.coinbase.com/exchange), [coinbase.com/prime](https://www.coinbase.com/prime), [coinbase.com/futures](https://www.coinbase.com/futures), [](https://www.coinbase.com/coinbase.com/developer-platform)coinbase.com/developer-platform, (each a “**Site**” and collectively the "**Sites**") or when you use the Coinbase mobile app, the Coinbase Card App, Coinbase Exchange, Coinbase Prime, or Coinbase Custody application programming interface (“**API**”) or third party applications relying on such APIs (together, our “**Apps**”) and related services. 

If you reside outside of the UK and the European Economic Area (the “**EEA**”), accessing and using our Services means that you accept this Privacy Policy and its terms. 

It is important that you understand how we use your information. You should read this page in full, but below are the key highlights and some helpful links:

*   Our goal is to simplify your crypto experience. If you do not wish for your personal information to be collected, used, or disclosed as described in this Privacy Policy, or you are under 18 years of age, you should stop accessing our Services.
    *   We collect and use your information in order to provide and improve our Services and your experience, protect the security and integrity of our platform, and meet our legal obligations.
    
    *   To learn more, explore [**Section 1. What Information We Collect**](#what-information-we-collect) and [**Section 2. How We Use Your Information**](#how-we-use-your-information).
        *   We share your information with other Coinbase companies, as well as trusted third parties and service providers, in order to offer our Services and fulfill legal requirements.
    
    *   To learn more, explore [**Section 3. How And Why We Share Your Information**](#how-and-why-we-share-your-information).
        *   We offer privacy tools for you to request access to or deletion of information we hold about you. You can use these tools by visiting your [Privacy Rights Dashboard](https://www.coinbase.com/settings/privacy-rights). Depending on where you live, you may also have other privacy rights under law.
    *   If you have any questions, please contact us on our [Support Portal](https://help.coinbase.com/en/contact-us?product=coinbase) or at dpo@coinbase.com. See [**Section 10. How to Contact Us With Questions**](#how-to-contact-us-with-questions) for more information.
    *   This translation is provided for informational purposes only. In the event of any discrepancy between the English text and this translation, the English version shall prevail.

1\. WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect the following personal information and documentation:

Information You Provide to Us

󰀐

| Information Category | Description |
| --- | --- |
| Basic Customer Information | Name<br><br>Address<br><br>Date of birth<br><br>Nationality<br><br>Country of residence<br><br>Gender<br><br>Phone number<br><br>Email Address |
| Supplemental Identification Information | Utility bills (for your billing address)<br><br>Photographs and/or videos<br><br>Government-issued identity document, e.g. passport, driver’s license, or state identification card<br><br>Social security or social insurance number<br><br>Employment information (e.g. company  name, job title, salary info) <br><br>Proof of residency, including visa information <br><br>Spouse name <br><br>Spouse Tax Identification Number |
| Electronic Identification (“EIDV”) Information | Biometric information generated based on photos or videos you provide in order for us to verify your identity |
| Institutional Information (if you are an institutional Customer) | Employer identification number (or comparable number issued by a government)<br><br>Personal identification information for all material beneficial owners of your business |
| Financial Information | Bank account number<br><br>Payment card primary account number ("PAN")<br><br>Trading and investment experience<br><br>Tax identification number of every tax residency<br><br>All Jurisdiction(s) (countries) of tax residence  <br><br>Income/net assets/wealth verification statements <br><br>Country residency Information necessary for tax purposes |
| Wallet Information | When you sign up to the Base App (formerly known as Coinbase Wallet), and connect it to your Coinbase account, we collect your Wallet address and information related to integrations that you select |
| Preferences | Settings and preferences you select in the Coinbase app |
| Transaction Information | Information about the transactions made on our Services, such as the name of the sender, the name of the recipient, the amount, currency preferences, payment method, date, and/or timestamp |
| Additional information submitted to us | Communications: Survey responses, information (including call recordings) provided to our Customer Support team or User Research team, including communications with interfaces such as our chatbots.<br><br>Referral Information: Your contacts’ phone or email addresses if you choose to invite friends to Coinbase.<br><br>Third Party Information: Information  provided when a user requires support or assistance in using our services. |

Information Collected Automatically

󰀐

| Information Category | Description |
| --- | --- |
| App, browser, and device information | Information about the device, operating system, and browser you’re using<br><br>Other device characteristics or identifiers (e.g. plugins, the network you connect to)<br><br>IP address<br><br>We may also temporarily collect information  about limited applications that you are connected to establish that connection |
| Product Usage Information | Activity information: Information about what you view or click on while visiting our Sites and Apps and how you use our Services<br><br>Diagnostic and Troubleshooting Information: Information about how our Services are performing when you use them, i.e. service-related diagnostic and performance information, including timestamps, crash data, website performance logs, and error messages or reports |
| Information from cookies and similar technologies | See our [Cookies Policy](https://www.coinbase.com/legal/cookie) for more information |

Information we obtain from Affiliates and third parties

󰀐

| Information Category | Description |
| --- | --- |
| Coinbase Group of Companies (“Affiliates”) | We may obtain information about you, such as Basic Customer Information, Transaction Information and Product Usage Information, from our Affiliates as a normal part of conducting business. For instance, if you link your various Coinbase accounts e.g. your Base account or your Coinbase Commerce account, we may utilize your Wallet Information and Financial Information in order to convert cryptocurrency into fiat and allow you to make withdrawals into your bank account. For more information, please see [Section 3. How and Why We Share Your Information](#how-and-why-we-share-your-information) |
| Public Database Information | We obtain information about you from public databases, such as the United Nations Sanctions List, US ITA Consolidated Screening List, and the SEC EDGAR, including your name, address, email address, phone number, gender, national ID number and nationality/country of residence, date of birth, job role, public employment profile, listing on any sanctions lists maintained by public authorities, and other data as necessary |
| Blockchain Data | We may analyze public blockchain data, including timestamps of transactions or events, transaction IDs, digital signatures, transaction amounts, and wallet addresses |
| Information from our Marketing and Advertising Partners | We receive information such as your name and contact information from our marketing partners, including in some instances what marketing content you viewed or the  actions you take on and off our Sites and  Apps, to better understand your preferences  and customize the ads that you see. |
| Information from Analytics Providers | We receive information about your usage of our Sites and Apps, interactions, age group, and survey responses (including prior to account creation, in some cases) |
| Retail Merchant Information | If you use your Coinbase account to conduct a transaction with a third party merchant, the merchant may provide us with data about you, such as your name and contact details, and your transaction with that merchant |
| Research and In-App Survey Information | We use third party service providers to conduct in-app surveys to better understand our Customers’ experience and improve our Services. The information we receive from our research partners is pseudonymous |

2\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We use your personal information to deliver, personalize, operate, improve, create, and develop our Services, to provide you with a secure, smooth, efficient and customized experience as you use them, and for legal compliance, loss prevention, and anti-fraud purposes. Learn more about how we use your personal information and our legal basis for each such data use:

Data use necessary to perform our contract with you

󰀐

We use certain information that is necessary to conclude and perform our [Customer Agreement](https://www.coinbase.com/legal/user_agreement/) or other relevant contract(s) with you. We will need to terminate your account if we cannot process your personal information for such purposes.

| Why and How We Use Your Information | Information Categories Used |
| --- | --- |
| To create and maintain your Coinbase account. In order to provide you with our Services, and to allow you to set up a customer account and profile. | Basic Customer Information<br><br>Supplemental Identification Information, Financial Information, Preferences |
| To provide you with Consumer Services | Basic Customer Information |
| In order to provide you with personalized  Services to invest (such as buy or sell),  save, earn, spend, stake, and borrow within  your account, including hosting and maintaining your digital wallets, including  your E-Money Wallet, Digital Currency  Wallet, and Web3 Wallet (when you connect them to your Coinbase account) and to provide you with [Verified by Coinbase.](https://www.coinbase.com/onchain-verify) | Supplemental Identification Information, Financial Information, Institutional Information, Transaction Information, Wallet Information , Preferences, Blockchain Data, Product Usage Information, Additional information submitted to us (not including Referral Information, which we  do not retain) |
| To provide you with Institutional Services<br><br>In order to provide Services to you, investors and institutions to allow investing,  payment, asset listings, and account management. | Basic Customer Information<br><br>Supplemental Identification Information, Financial Information, Institutional Information, Additional information submitted to us, Wallet Information, Transaction Information |
| To provide you with Coinbase Pay  <br><br>In order to provide you with Coinbase Pay,  a payment feature that allows you to buy or  transfer supported crypto on Coinbase to  your wallet, and Direct Deposit, which  allows you to get your salary paid in the  cryptocurrency of your choice, asset  controls, and connects merchants to Users  or Customers to allow acceptance and  provision of crypto payments. | Basic Customer Information<br><br>Supplemental Identification, Information, Financial Information, Preferences |
| To provide you with Developer Platform Services <br><br>In order to provide you with our Coinbase Developer Platform services, which  offers tools, APIs and infrastructure for Web3 development and staking services. <br><br>We may also process your information for  the purposes of providing a functional  preview of a Coinbase Developer mobile  application or API capability and decide. | Basic Customer Information<br><br>Supplemental Identification Information_,_ Transaction Information, Wallet Information, Financial Information, Preferences, Blockchain Data |
| To provide you with Coinbase Verifications<br><br>To generate, process, and store attestation data based on your status as a trade eligible Coinbase user (assuming you meet the eligibility criteria). | Basic Customer Information <br><br>Supplemental Identification Information <br><br>Wallet Information <br><br>Transaction information |
| To provide you with access to Verified Pools <br><br>To provide access to Verified Pools, a  blockchain protocol that enables Users that  have been attested to by Coinbase. <br><br>Verifications to provide liquidity and swap  crypto-assets via third party liquidity pools. | Wallet Information <br><br>Transaction information <br><br>App, browser, and device information |
| To provide customer support <br><br>To address your request for support in the  Apps, via the Sites or by email and to  respond to customer care and other inquiries, including providing telephone based premium customer support to  Customers (who provide their telephone  numbers), chat message support (including  chatbots), and social media support. | Basic Customer Information <br><br>Supplemental Identification Information, Transaction Information<br><br>Product Usage Information including Location  Information<br><br>Preferences <br><br>Additional information submitted to us |
| To send Service communications <br><br>To send you administrative or account related communications about our Services,  which can include security updates or  transaction-related information, through  email, telephone, or in-product/push  notifications. You may not opt-out of  receiving critical service communications,  such as emails or mobile notifications sent  for legal or security purposes. | Basic Customer Information<br><br>Product Usage Information<br><br>Additional information submitted to us <br><br>Preferences <br><br>Transaction Information |
| To promote the safety, security and integrity  of our Services <br><br>To verify accounts and related activity, find  and address violations of our Customer [Agreement](https://www.coinbase.com/legal/user_agreement/united_states) or policies (including our [Prohibited & Conditional Use Policy](https://www.coinbase.com/legal/prohibited_use)),  investigate suspicious activity, detect,  prevent and combat harmful or unlawful  behaviour, detect fraudulent behaviour and  to maintain the integrity of our Services,  including account takeover (“ATO”)  prevention and support. <br><br>We may utilize automated decision-making  for fulfilling our regulatory and contractual  obligations in relation to the safety, security and integrity of our Services. This includes to: verify accounts and their activities; detect and prevent suspicious behaviors such as unlawful or fraudulent actions; and maintain the integrity of our Services,  particularly in preventing account takeovers. | Basic Customer Information <br><br>Transaction Information <br><br>Product Usage Information <br><br>Supplemental Identification Information, Institutional Information <br><br>Financial Information<br><br>Additional information submitted to us |

Data use to comply with our legal obligations

󰀐

Our Services are subject to laws and regulations requiring us to collect, use, and store your personal information in certain ways. If you do not provide the personal information required by law, we will have to close your account.

| Why and How We Use Your Information | Information Categories Used |
| --- | --- |
| To verify your identity <br><br>We are generally required to collect various  pieces of personal information to properly  identify or verify your identity and comply  with other specific anti-money laundering  (“AML”) or sanctions laws/regulations (e.g.  funds transfer rules). Our verification  processes also involve electronic  identification through the comparison of  your ‘selfie’ against your provided  verification information. Coinbase implements and requires its  service providers to implement reasonable  security measures to protect this information, which is only disclosed  where permitted by law.  <br><br>If you nominate a guardian or trusted  contact, we will collect their email address  in order to send an email invitation for them  to accept. | Basic Customer Information,<br><br>Supplemental Identification Information, <br><br>EIDV Information |
| To determine your legal eligibility for certain regulated products <br><br>When you use certain locally regulated  products or engage in certain advanced  trading activities, we may be required to  carry out additional checks to ensure your  suitability (e.g. under the European Market  Infrastructure Regulation). | Basic Customer Information <br><br>Financial Information <br><br>Supplemental Identification Information |
| To comply with other legal and regulatory  obligations<br><br>We may access, read, preserve, and  disclose information when we believe it is  reasonably necessary to comply with law,  legal obligations, regulations, law  enforcement, governmental, and other legal  requests, court orders, or for disclosure to  tax authorities.  <br><br>Examples of laws that may require us to  collect, use or disclose your information: <br><br>Civil, commercial, criminal, or  consumer protection matters:  where we are in receipt of a court  order to disclose information for the purposes of court proceedings or regulatory inquiries (e.g. orders or mandatory requests under the Irish Competition and Consumer Protection  Act 2014, U.S. federal and state consumer protection and privacy laws,  Canadian consumer protection and privacy laws, subpoenas from any court with jurisdiction, and/or Singapore Criminal Procedure Code  2010).  <br><br>Corporate and taxation matters: obligations such as the Irish Companies Act 2014 and the Taxes Consolidation Act 1997, the Internal Revenue Service Code, and the Common Reporting Standard<br><br>Regulatory matters: to comply with  our regulatory obligations, including engaging with our regulators, such as  (but not limited to) the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission, the National Futures Association, the U.S. Securities and  Exchange Commission, the Financial  Transactions Reports and Analysis Centre of Canada, any Canadian securities regulatory authority or regulator, the Canadian Investment Regulatory Organization, the Central  Bank of Ireland, the UK Financial Conduct Authority, the German federal financial supervisory authority (“BaFin”), the Monetary Authority of Singapore, the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission  (“CySEC”), and the Australian Securities and Investments Commission. | Basic Customer Information<br><br>Supplemental Identification Information Institutional Information<br><br>Wallet Information<br><br>Financial Information <br><br>Transaction Information <br><br>Product Usage Information<br><br>Additional information submitted to us (not including Referral Information, which we do not  retain) <br><br>Blockchain Data |

Data use for our Legitimate Interests

󰀐

Where permitted by applicable laws, we rely on our legitimate interests or those of third parties  (like our other Customers and in some cases, the general public), provided that those legitimate  interests are not outweighed by your rights and freedoms. In the EEA and UK, you have the right  to object to, and seek the restriction of, this processing. See Section 8. Your Privacy Rights and  Choices for more information. For certain jurisdictions where legitimate interests may not be  available or appropriate, we rely on other legal bases such as consent.

| Why and How We Use Your Information | Legitimate Interests Relied On | Information Categories Used |
| --- | --- | --- |
| To customize your experience with our  Services and otherwise improve our  Services <br><br>In order to perform core metrics, customize  your experience with our Services and to  generally improve our Services, we collect  information about your online activity while  you are using the Services (for example,  when and how often pages on our Sites and Apps are visited, and our Services are  used). | It is in our interest to  understand how you  interact with the  Services in order to  customize and/or  improve our products  and Services and  enable accurate and  reliable reporting. | Basic Customer  <br><br>Information<br><br>Product Usage  <br><br>Information <br><br>Preferences<br><br>Transaction Information |
| To provide marketing communications to  you <br><br>In a manner consistent with our regulatory obligations, we use your  information to send you targeted marketing  communications through email, mobile, in app and push notifications or by SMS. You may also see ads for our Services  when you visit other apps and websites. | It is in our interest to  promote Coinbase products and Services  that you may be interested in. | Basic Customer  <br><br>Information<br><br>Institutional Information <br><br>Product Usage  <br><br>Information<br><br>Transaction Information <br><br>Preferences<br><br>Information from our  Marketing Partners <br><br>Additional information submitted to us |
| To provide you with promotions and issue  grants <br><br>We use your information to provide promotions, including sweepstakes offers or other incentives and rewards for using  our Services, and to issue grants as part of  Coinbase Developer Services. | It is in our interest and  your interest to reward  customer loyalty. | Basic Customer  <br><br>Information <br><br>Wallet Information<br><br>Supplemental  <br><br>Identification Information _(if you are in Brazil, Australia, or Singapore, your consent will be required in case we process supplemental identification  information for this specific processing activity. Otherwise, we rely on our legitimate interest.)_<br><br>Transaction Information Preferences |
| We preserve and share information with  others, including law enforcement, civil  litigants, and others who may issue legal  requests (_If you are in Brazil, Australia, or Singapore, we rely on legal bases of compliance with a legal obligation or to guarantee fraud prevention and security of the data subject in process of identification and authentication in electronic systems.)_<br><br>Where not otherwise required by law, and  depending on the circumstances, we may  preserve and share your information: <br><br>In response to requests from third  parties, such as civil litigants, law  enforcement, and other government  authorities, for example to assist  authorities in the investigation of fraud;<br><br>Promote the safety, security, and  integrity of the Coinbase Service, network, our Customers, Users, employees, property and the public; <br><br>When we seek to protect ourselves in  the context of litigation or other disputes, such as violations of our  Customer Agreement and policies; and/or <br><br>Respond to Customer/claimant  requests or communications, reviewing Customer accounts and  transactions for litigation disputes, and  recording account details for litigation  and settlement purposes. | It is in our interest and  the interest of the  general public to  prevent and address  fraud, unauthorized  use of the Services,  violations of our terms  or policies, or other  harmful or illegal  activity; to protect  ourselves (including  our rights, Coinbase  personnel and  property or the  Service), our  Customers or others,  including as part of investigations or  regulatory inquiries; to  defend our legal rights  and resolve disputes;  to secure our platform  and network, to verify  accounts and activity,  to combat harmful  conduct, to detect,  prevent and address  fraud, abuse, spam  and other bad  experiences or to  prevent death or  imminent bodily harm. | Basic Customer Information, <br><br>Wallet Information <br><br>Supplemental Identification Information <br><br>Institutional Information<br><br>Transaction Information<br><br>Product Usage Information <br><br>Additional information  submitted to us (not including Referral Information, which we do  not retain) <br><br>Blockchain Data |
| To promote safety, security and integrity _(If you are in Brazil, we rely on legal bases of compliance with a legal obligation or to guarantee fraud prevention and security of the data subject in process of identification and authentication in electronic systems )_<br><br>Outside of performing our contract with you,  we may use and analyze your information  to protect the integrity of our Services. For example, we may use it to: <br><br>Log customer reports and patterns of  suspicious behaviour to understand techniques being used by bad actors  who may wish to interfere with the Services;<br><br>To identify and investigate patterns of  suspicious behaviour or violations of  our policies and Terms; and <br><br>To link and combine datasets for security and vulnerability identification  purposes. | It is in our interest and  the interests of our Users and Customers  to secure our platform  and network, to verify  accounts and activity,  to combat harmful conduct, to detect, prevent and address  fraud, abuse, spam  and other bad experiences. | Any of the categories  of information listed in  Section 1. What Information We Collect. |
| To research and innovate <br><br>We carry out surveys of your experience  using the Services and the trading that you  engage in to conduct and support research  and innovation on topics related to our  Services. <br><br>We may also contact non-Coinbase customers via our third party service  providers for the purposes of participating in  Coinbase’s research studies. | It is in our interest and  our Customers’  interest to improve  and iterate our  Services through  information obtained  from these research  surveys and  interviews. | Basic Customer  Information <br><br>Transaction Information<br><br>Product Usage  <br><br>Information <br><br>Communications <br><br>Research and In-App  Survey Information |
| To comply with our contractual obligations  with third parties <br><br>We keep contracts with third party vendors  and service providers that are necessary to  improve or make available certain services,  options or solutions to you. In those  circumstances, we may process and share  your personal information with these third  party vendors or service providers to  comply with our contractual obligations and  maintain the services, options or solutions  available | It is in our interest to perform any contractual obligation  assumed with third parties. It is also our  Customers’ interest to access  improvements in our  Services resulting from our contracts with third party  vendors and service  providers. | Basic Customer Information, Transaction Information<br><br>Additional information submitted to us <br><br>Information from our Marketing Partners <br><br>Preferences |

Data use based on your consent

󰀐

When we use your information based on your consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time on a go-forward basis (which will not affect our prior use of your data, based on your previously given consent). You may change your device-based or in-app settings anytime as described in [Section 7. Your Privacy Rights and Choices.](#your-privacy-rights-and-choices)

| Why and How We Use Your Information | Information Categories Used |
| --- | --- |
| Where you ask us to share your  data <br><br>Where you direct us to share your personal  data with a third party, we may do so. For  example, you may authorize third parties to  act on your behalf (such as a financial  advisor, lawyer, accountant or family  member or guardian under a power of  attorney). We may need to ask for proof that  a third party has been validly authorised to  act on your behalf. | Basic Customer Information<br><br>Supplemental Information <br><br>Financial Information <br><br>Transaction Information <br><br>Additional information submitted to us |
| To enable device-based settings <br><br>Collecting information that you allow us to  receive through the device-based settings  you enable (such as access to your GPS  location, camera or photos) which we use to  provide the features or services described  when you enable the setting. | App, browser, and device information |
| To provide marketing communications to you <br><br>To send you targeted marketing  communications through email, mobile, in app, and push notifications or by SMS. You may also see ads for our Services  when you visit other apps and websites. | Basic Customer Information<br><br>Institutional Information<br><br>Product Usage Information<br><br>Transaction Information<br><br>Information from our Marketing Partners <br><br>Preferences <br><br>Additional information submitted to us |

Data use to protect your or others’ vital interests

󰀐

| Why and How We Use Your Information | Information Categories Used |
| --- | --- |
| Preserving, reviewing, and sharing information with law enforcement and others<br><br>We may preserve, review, and share information with law enforcement and others in circumstances where someone’s vital interests require protection, such as in the case of emergencies. For example, where there is a risk to the well-being or life of a Coinbase Customer. | Basic Customer Information<br><br>Supplemental Identification Information<br><br>Institutional Information<br><br>Wallet Information<br><br>Transaction Information<br><br>Product Usage Information<br><br>Additional information submitted to us (not including Referral Information, which we do not retain)<br><br>Blockchain Data |
| To protect vulnerable customers<br><br>In certain jurisdictions, under financial and  consumer protection regulations, Coinbase has additional obligations to vulnerable  customers. It is in the substantial public interest for Coinbase to provide additional support if you are or become a vulnerable  customer. | Basic Customer Information<br><br>Supplemental Identification Information<br><br>Institutional Information<br><br>Wallet Information<br><br>Transaction Information<br><br>Product Usage Information<br><br>Additional information submitted to us<br><br>Blockchain Data |

If you reside outside the United Kingdom or EEA, the purposes for which we may use your  information are as described above, however, the legal bases on which we rely in your jurisdiction may differ from those listed above (e.g., your consent may be considered as the principal  basis on which we may use your personal information for all purposes).

If you provide Coinbase or our service providers and agents with personal information of another  individual, you represent that you have all necessary authority and/or have obtained all necessary  consents from such person to enable us to collect, use and disclose such personal information for  the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.

3\. HOW AND WHY WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

We work with service providers, partners and other third parties to help us provide our Services, and as a result we need to share certain information with these third parties.  Here’s how:

Affiliates

󰀐

Personal information that we process and collect may be transferred between companies, Services, and employees affiliated with us as a normal part of conducting business and offering our Services to you. See [Section 11. Our Relationship With You](#our-relationship-with-you) for a list of our affiliated companies and Services.

Linked Third Party Websites

󰀐

When you use third-party services (like when you connect your Coinbase account with your bank account) or websites that are linked through our Services, the providers of those services or products may receive information about you that Coinbase, you, or others share with them. Please note that when you use third-party services or Coinbase Affiliate Services which are not governed by this Privacy Policy, their own terms and privacy policies will govern your use of those services and products.

Travel Rule

󰀐

In accordance with regulations commonly known as the “TraveI Rule” in multiple jurisdictions, Coinbase may collect, retain, and/or share with other service providers information about the counterparties in certain cryptocurrency transfers. For example, Coinbase may collect  counterparty information when you receive a deposit of cryptocurrency from outside of the Coinbase platform or when you send cryptocurrency to a non-Coinbase wallet address. In some instances, Coinbase may further be obligated under the Travel Rule to provide information about you and/or  the counterparty to the virtual asset service provider (or applicable regional equivalent) (“VASP”)  that is transferring cryptocurrency to, or receiving it from, Coinbase. To do this, Coinbase employs  tools such as TRUST (the Travel Rule Universal Solution Technology) – a global, secure, and  industry-driven solution designed to comply with the Travel Rule while helping to protect your security  and privacy.

Professional advisors, industry partners, authorities and regulators

󰀐

Professional advisors, industry partners (and their service providers), authorities and  regulators. We share your information described in [Section 1. What Information We Collect](#what-information-we-collect) with our advisors, regulators, tax authorities, law enforcement, government agencies, and industry  partners (and their service providers) to: 

a) respond pursuant to applicable law or regulations, court orders, legal process or government requests;  

b) comply with our reporting and information sharing obligations with industry partners,  including other and regulatory authorities;

c) detect, investigate, prevent, or address fraud and other illegal activity or security and  technical issues;

d) protect the rights, property, and safety of our Customers, Coinbase and its Affiliates, or  others, including to prevent death or imminent bodily harm; and

e) to facilitate subscription, transfer or redemption requests.

Asset Transfer or Company Acquisition

󰀐

We may choose to buy or sell assets, and may share and/or transfer information about our Customers in connection with the evaluation of and entry into such transactions. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, merged, reorganized, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control or similar event, your personal information could be one of the assets transferred to the acquiring party. 

Third-Party Service Providers

󰀐

We work with third-party service providers to help us provide or  promote our Services. This involves disclosing to our third-party service providers conversion data,  including IP address, with advertisers such as Meta to create custom audience lists and AppLovin.  (See here for more information about AppLovin’s collection and use of your information). These third party service providers will match this information with their user data (gathered in accordance with  their own privacy policies and terms of service) to allow us to target ads to groups of individuals who  have interacted with us. 

When we share  information with third-party service providers in this capacity, we require them to use your information  on our behalf in accordance with our instructions and terms and only process as necessary for the  purpose of the contract.  

We work with different types of third-party service providers, including:

| Types of Third-Party Service Providers We Use | What Information We Share |
| --- | --- |
| [Third-Party Electronic ID Verification Service Vendors](https://www.coinbase.com/legal/privacy/third-party-verification-vendors), including those that process biometric information<br><br>Vendors for tax reporting<br><br>Derivatives service providers<br><br>Retail merchants (to provide rewards/incentives)<br><br>Marketing and promotions providers (to promote our Services)<br><br>Telecommunications technology providers (to send you messages, including SMS messages)<br><br>CTF/AML service providers (for the purposes of transaction monitoring)<br><br>Data hosting service providers and payment vendors (for off-site data hosting)<br><br>Security service providers (for investigating fraud and security incidents)<br><br>Analytics providers (to understand how you use our Services)<br><br>Payment processing companies (to process transactions on our behalf)<br><br>Document repository services providers<br><br>Customer support vendors<br><br>Digital asset advocacy groups like Stand With Crypto | Basic Customer Information<br><br>Supplemental Identification Information<br><br>EIDV Information<br><br>Financial Information<br><br>Institutional Information<br><br>Usage Information<br><br>Transaction Information<br><br>Blockchain Data<br><br>Wallet Information<br><br>App, browser, and devise information<br><br>Additional information submitted to us |

4\. HOW WE HOLD YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We generally hold your information electronically in our servers or those of our trusted service  providers. On occasion, we hold your information in hard copy. We implement reasonable technical  and organizational safeguards to protect the information we hold, and we require our service  providers to do the same.

5\. HOW LONG WE RETAIN YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We retain your information as needed to provide our Services, comply with legal obligations, or protect our or others’ interests. While retention requirements vary by country, we maintain internal  retention policies on the basis of how information needs to be used. This includes considerations  such as when the information was collected or created, whether it is necessary in order to continue offering you our Services, whether we are required to hold the information to comply with our legal  obligations, including AML/KYC compliance, or other financial regulatory obligations, or information preservation requirements. We also keep certain information where necessary to protect the safety, security and integrity of our Services, Customers, and Users. We may keep pseudonymised personal information (information with identifying details removed or replaced) and your user ID to help us understand usage patterns and improve our services. We retain biometric information (as part of our retention of Supplemental Identification Information) for the period required for financial regulatory compliance or otherwise as required by applicable law. Our third-party electronic identity verification service providers retain this information for as  long as set out in their [applicable notices/policies](https://www.coinbase.com/legal/privacy/third-party-verification-vendors). In line with these considerations, we delete information that is no longer needed for the above  purposes when you close your account, or when you request deletion of your information, or if required under applicable law, when you withdraw consent to us using your information (which you can initiate through your [Privacy Rights Dashboard](https://www.coinbase.com/settings/privacy-rights)).

6\. CHILDREN'S PERSONAL INFORMATION

The Sites and Services are not directed to persons under the age of 18, and we do not knowingly request or collect any information about persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not provide any personal information through the Sites or Services. If a User or Customer submitting personal information is suspected of being younger than 18 years of age, Coinbase will require the relevant Customer or User to close his or her account, and will take steps to delete the individual’s information as soon as possible.

7\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS

To facilitate our global operations, Coinbase, its Affiliates, third-party partners, and service providers may transfer, store, and process your personal information throughout the world, including Ireland, Germany, Singapore, the UK, the US, and the Philippines. [See here for more information](https://www.coinbase.com/legal/privacy/international-transfers). 

If you reside in the EEA, Switzerland, or the United Kingdom, we rely upon a variety of legal mechanisms to facilitate these transfers of your personal information (collectively, “**European Personal Data**”).

*   We rely primarily on the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses to facilitate the international and onward transfer of European Personal Data to third countries, including from our EU operating entities to Coinbase, Inc. in the United States. For a copy of the Standard Contractual Clauses, please contact dpo@coinbase.com. *   In addition, we may rely on certain exemptions provided for under data protection law for our international transfers. We also rely on [adequacy decisions](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/adequacy-decisions_en) from the European Commission where available and exemptions provided for under data protection law. For example, because Coinbase operates and provides its Services globally, we need to share information with our Affiliates and to data centers outside the EEA in order to develop, offer, and improve our Services (Article 49(1)(b) GDPR). In addition, we may rely on certain exemptions for sharing personal information with law enforcement outside of the EEA in emergency situations (Article 49(1)(f) GDPR).

EU-US, UK-US, and Swiss-US  Data Privacy Framework

Coinbase complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) (together referred to as the “Data Privacy Frameworks”) and the DPF Principles as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Coinbase has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to:

*   the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF;
    *   the UK-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-UK DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF; and
    *   the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF.  

In the context of an onward transfer, Coinbase has responsibility for the processing of personal data it receives under the DPF and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as a service provider, partner and/or other third party to help us provide our Services on our behalf (as described in Section 4 of this policy). Coinbase remains liable under the DPF if any such third party processes personal data in a manner inconsistent with the DPF, unless Coinbase can prove that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy  and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles (together, the “Principles”), the Principles shall govern.

To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/)  

In compliance with the Data Privacy Frameworks, Coinbase commits to resolve all DPF Principles-related complaints about our collection and use of your personal information.  EU, UK, and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our handling of personal data received in reliance on the relevant Data Privacy Frameworks should first contact Coinbase at: [dpo@coinbase.com](mailto:dpo@coinbase.com) 

For unresolved complaints concerning our handling of personal information in reliance on the Data Privacy Frameworks, Coinbase is a member of and relies upon the ICDR-AAA services for the Data Privacy Framework Program, see here [https://go.adr.org/dpf\_irm.html](https://go.adr.org/dpf_irm.html), which may involve, under certain conditions, binding arbitration.

The U.S. Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over Coinbase’s compliance with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF).

If you reside in Brazil, we may rely upon a variety of legal mechanisms to facilitate international data  transfers of your personal information. 

a) We rely primarily on the Standard Contractual Clauses approved by the National Data  Protection Authority to facilitate the international and onward transfer of personal data to third  countries, including from our Brazilian subsidiary to Coinbase, Inc. in the United States. The  approved SCCs can also include equivalent SCCs, as provided by Article 20 of Regulation  no. 19/2024 by ANPD. For a copy of the Standard Contractual Clauses, please contact  dpo@coinbase.com 

b) In addition, we may rely on certain exemptions provided for under Brazilian data protection  laws for our international transfers. We also rely on adequacy decisions from the National  Data Protection Authority where available. 

The mechanisms abovementioned will not apply when you have a direct relationship with any  company located outside Brazil, because this situation is not considered an international data  transfer (Article 7, III, of Regulation no. 19/2024, from ANPD). 

If you reside in Argentina, we may rely upon a variety of legal mechanisms to facilitate international  data transfers of your personal information. 

c) We rely primarily on the European Standard Contractual Clauses as set forth above. 

d) In addition, we may rely on certain exemptions provided for under Argentine data protection  laws for our international transfers. We also rely on the adequacy decision issued through  Disposition E60/2016 of the Argentine Data Protection Authority where available.

8\. YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS AND CHOICES

Depending on where you live, you may be able to exercise certain privacy rights related to your personal information. For any of your privacy rights and choices referenced below, requests relating to your personal information can be made by logging into your account and going to your [Privacy Rights Dashboard](https://www.coinbase.com/settings/privacy-rights) or by submitting a request via our [Support Portal](https://help.coinbase.com/en) or by contacting our Data  Protection Officer at [dpo@coinbase.com](mailto:dpo@coinbase.com). If any of the rights listed below are not provided under law for your operating entity or jurisdiction, Coinbase has absolute discretion in providing you with these rights.

*   **Right to access and portability**_:_ 
    
    *   You may request that we provide you a copy of your personal information held by us through your [Privacy Rights Dashboard](https://www.coinbase.com/settings/privacy-rights), or by submitting a request via our [Support Portal](https://help.coinbase.com/en/contact-us?product=coinbase). *   **Right to rectification**_:_ 
    
    *   You may request us to rectify or update any of your personal information held by  Coinbase that is incomplete or inaccurate by logging in to your account and going to the Profile or My Account page. If you cannot access or update particular information through those pages, then you can submit a request via our Support  Portal or by emailing dpo@coinbase.com.
        *   **Right to deletion/erasure**_:_ 
    
    *   You may request to erase your personal information, subject to applicable law. If you close your Coinbase Account, we will retain or delete information associated with your account as described in [**Section 4. How Long We Keep Your Personal Information**](#how-long-we-keep-your-information)**.**
        *   **Right to withdraw your consent**_:_ 
    
    *   To the extent the processing of your personal information is based on your consent, you may withdraw your consent at any time. The lawfulness of Coinbase’s processing before you withdraw your consent will not be affected by such withdrawal.
        *   **Right to object to or restrict processing**_:_ 
    
    *   You may have the right to restrict or object to us using or transferring your personal  information based on our legitimate interests, in the public interest, or for direct  marketing. To do so, please submit a request to dpo@coinbase.com. We may  continue to process your personal information where permitted or required by  applicable law. You can opt-out of receiving marketing communications from  Coinbase through your account settings or by submitting a request via our [Support Portal](https://help.coinbase.com/en/contact-us?product=coinbase) or at dpo@coinbase.com. If you reside in India, we will endeavour to resolve  any complaint or grievance that you may have regarding our use of your personal  information within 30 days or such other time-period as may be permitted under  applicable law.
        *   **Right to non-discrimination**: We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights provided to you under law.
    *   **Right to lodge a complaint:**  
    
    *   If you have a complaint about our practices with respect to your personal information, you can submit it via our Support Portal or by emailing us at dpo@coinbase.com. We take all complaints seriously and will respond within a reasonable time.
        *   If you reside in the EEA, Switzerland, or the UK, you have the right to lodge a complaint about our practices with respect to your personal information with the supervisory authority of your country or state. In the UK, the relevant data protection authority is the Information Commissioner's Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, +44 (0303) 123 1113, email: casework@ico.org.uk. In Ireland, the relevant data protection authority is the Data Protection Commission, 21 Fitzwilliam Square South, Dublin 2, D02 RD28, +353 017650100 / + 353 1800437737, email: info@dataprotection.ie or by using the following online form: [Forms for Data Protection](https://forms.dataprotection.ie/contact). In Luxemburg, the relevant data protection authority is the National Commission for Data Protection (CNPD) at Commission Nationale pour la Protection des Donnees, Service des plaints, 15, Boulevard du Jazz, L-4370 Belvaux, Luxembourg, Tél. : (+352) 26 10 60 -1.
        *   If you reside in Australia, the Philippines, or India, you may lodge a complaint about our practices with respect to your personal information with the supervisory authority of your country. In Australia, the relevant data protection authority is the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner, and complaints may be made through their website at [www.oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/). In the Philippines, the relevant data protection authority is the National Privacy Commission, email: complaints@privacy.gov.ph.
        *   If you reside in Canada, you may contact the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of  Canada using the appropriate contact mechanism based on the nature of your inquiry  (see https://www.priv.gc.ca/en/report-a-concern/ for more details). However, we  would appreciate hearing from you directly before you contact the Office in order to  attempt to assist you as quickly as possible. Please see section “9. How to Contact  Us With Questions” for our contact details.
        *   If you reside in Brazil, you may lodge a complaint about our practices with respect to  your personal information with the Data Protection National Authority (“ANPD”), and  complaints may be made through their website: https://www.gov.br/pt br/servicos/abrir-requerimento-relacionado-a-lgpd. *   If your reside in Argentina, the Agency for Public Information Access, in its capacity  as Control Agency of Law 25,326, is responsible for dealing with complaints and  claims filed by those whose rights are affected by non-compliance with the regulations  in force regarding the protection of personal data. The data owner shall have the right  to access his personal data for free, once every six (6) months or on a shorter basis  if a legitimate interest is demonstrated, as established by Section 14, Sub Section 3  of Law 25,326.
        *   **Right to obtain identities of third-party recipients**: If you reside in India, you may request  for details of all third-parties with whom your personal information has been shared along  with a description of personal information shared.
    *   **Right to nominate**: If you reside in India, you may appoint any other individual to exercise  your rights with respect to your personal information in the event of your death or incapacity.

To protect your privacy and security, we may take steps to verify your identity before complying with your request and we may decline your request if we are unable to verify your identity.

Under certain US data privacy laws, you may also designate an authorized agent to make these requests on your behalf. 

_These rights are not absolute, and may be denied: (a) when granting access or assisting portability would adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others; (b) to protect our rights and properties; (c) where the request is frivolous or vexatious; or (d) as otherwise permitted by law._

9\. PRIVACY NOTICE FOR UNITED STATES RESIDENTS

If you are a United States resident, you can learn more about how we use your information and your privacy rights by reviewing our [United States Privacy Notice](https://www.coinbase.com/legal/unitedstates-privacy-notice). Any terms defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act (as amended) (“**CCPA**”) have the same meaning when used in the US Privacy Notice.

10\. HOW TO CONTACT US WITH QUESTIONS

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, or if you have a complaint, please contact us on our [Support Portal](https://help.coinbase.com/en/contact-us?product=coinbase), at dpo@coinbase.com or by writing to us at the address of your Coinbase service provider (provided in [**Section 12. Our Relationship With You**](#our-relationship-with-you) below).

11\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We’re constantly trying to improve our Services, so we may need to change this Privacy Policy from time to time as well. We post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page and, where appropriate, we will provide you with reasonable notice of any material changes before they take effect or as otherwise required by law. The date the Privacy Policy was last updated is identified at the top of this page.

We may provide additional "just-in-time" disclosures or information about how we collect or use your information in the context of specific Services; these in-product notices may supplement or clarify our privacy practices or may provide you with additional choices about how we use your information.

12\. OUR RELATIONSHIP WITH YOU

If you reside in the EEA, Coinbase Ireland Limited, Coinbase Europe Limited and Coinbase Germany GmbH currently act as joint controllers in respect of your personal information. Coinbase Ireland Limited is the joint controller with primary responsibility for your personal information, including with respect to providing you with information and responding to any requests you may make under the GDPR.

With its new Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) authorisation, Coinbase Luxembourg S.A. will soon provide Crypto Asset Services to our EEA customers. Once this change comes into effect, you will  receive a notification from us with more details. At that point Coinbase Ireland Limited and Coinbase  Luxembourg S.A. will act as joint controllers in respect of your personal data and will be jointly  responsible for your personal information, including with respect to providing you with information  and responding to any requests you may make under the GDPR. 

You can contact either entity via our Data Protection Officer at dpo@coinbase.com or by writing to  us at the address of your Coinbase service provider. Please see more about how you can exercise  your rights under the GDPR through our [Privacy Rights Dashboard](https://www.coinbase.com/settings/privacy-rights).

CONSUMER/INSTITUTIONAL SERVICES

󰀐

NORTH AMERICA (UNITED STATES & CANADA)

| Where You Reside | Services Provided | Your Coinbase Service Provider | Contact Address |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| United States | Digital Asset Services, Fiat Wallet services | Coinbase, Inc. CA Entity No.: C3548456 | Coinbase, Inc. c/o C T Corporation System 818 West Seventh St., Ste. 930 Los Angeles, California 90017 |
| United States | Custodial Services | Coinbase Custody Trust Company, LLC (unless otherwise indicated in your service contract) NYS License # 122506 | Coinbase Custody Trust Company, LLC c/o C T Corporation System 28 Liberty Street New York, New York 10005 |
| United States | Credit and Lending Services | Coinbase Credit, Inc. CA Entity No.: C4315976 | Coinbase Credit, Inc. c/o C T Corporation System 818 West Seventh St., Ste. 930 Los Angeles, California 90017 |
| United States | Futures Trading | Coinbase Financial Markets, Inc. | 1 Madison Ave, 24th floor, New York, NY 10010, United States |
| United States | Broker Dealer Services | Coinbase Capital Markets Corporation | 1 Madison Ave., 24th Floor, New York, NY 10010, USA |
| Canada | Digital Asset Services, Fiat services | Coinbase Canada, Inc. | 1 University Avenue, #14- 111, Toronto ON M5J 2P1 CAN |

APAC

| Where You Reside | Services Provided | Your Coinbase Service Provider | Contact Address |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Singapore, New Zealand, Taiwan, Philippines, Hong Kong, South Korea, Taiwan, UAE. | Digital Asset Services, Fiat Wallet Services | Coinbase Singapore Pte. Ltd. Unique Entity No.: 201935002N | One Marina Boulevard, #28-00, Singapore 018989 |
| Australia | Digital Asset Services, Fiat Wallet Services | Coinbase Australia Pty Ltd; ACN 654 922 442 | Coinbase Australia c/o TMF Corporate Services (Aust) Pty Limited, Suite 1 Level 11, 66 Goulburn Street, Sydney NSW 2000 Australia |
| India | Digital Asset, Services, Digita l Asset Derivative, Services and Additional Coinbase Services | Coinbase India Private Limited through Coinbase Group. | Regus Elegance, 2F, Elegance Jasola District Centre, Old Mathura Road, New Delhi, 110025 |

EEA (European Economic Area)

| Where You Reside | Services Provided | Your Coinbase Service Provider | Contact Address |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| EEA | Digital Asset Services | Coinbase Europe Limited. Company No: 675475 | 70 Sir John Rogerson's  Quay Dublin 2, Ireland |
| Germany | Digital Asset Services | Coinbase Germany GmbH. Company No: HRB 213709 B. BaFin-ID 10158674 | Kurfürstendamm 22, 10719 Berlin, Germany |
| EEA | Fiat Wallet Services | Coinbase Ireland Limited. Company No: 630350 CBI Register No: C188493 | 70 Sir John Rogerson's Quay Dublin 2, Ireland |
| United Kingdom (and select non-EEA countries in Europe) | E-Money Services, Digital Asset Services and Additional Services | CB Payments, Ltd Company No: 09708629 FCA Register No: 900635 | The Scalpel, 18th Floor, 52 Lime Street, London, United Kingdom, EC3M 7AF |
| EEA | Digital Asset Services | Coinbase Luxembourg S.A. Company No: B292147  CSSF Register No: N00000004 | 5, Place de la Gare, L-1616, Luxembourg |
| EEA | Markets in Financial Instruments (“MifiD”) Services | Coinbase Financial Services Europe Limited (Registration number: HE350475) | 1 Lampousas Street, 1095, Nicosia, Cyprus |

OUTSIDE EU, US, UK, APAC

| Where You Reside | Services Provided | Your Coinbase Service Provider | Contact Address |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Eligible jurisdictions outside the United States | Digital Asset Services | Coinbase Bermuda Limited | Park Place, 55 Par La Ville  Road, Hamilton, HM11 Bermuda |
| Anywhere but the USA, UK, certain APAC regions, EEA | Digital Asset Services | Coinbase Bermuda Services Limited | Park Place, 55 Par La Ville Road, Hamilton, HM11 Bermuda |
| Brazil | Digital Asset Services | Coinbase Brasil Ltda | City of Sao Paulo, State of  Sao Paulo, at Alameda  Santos, 2300, Suite 11  part, Cerqueira Cesar, ZIP  Code 01418-200 |

DEVELOPER SERVICES

󰀐

| Where You Reside | Services Provided | Your Coinbase Service Provider | Contact Address |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Anywhere | Coinbase Pay SDK<br><br>Exchange API<br><br>Rosetta <br><br>Prime API <br><br>Sign In with Coinbase | Coinbase, Inc. CA Entity  No.: C4315976 | Coinbase, Inc. c/o C T Corporation System 818 West Seventh St., Ste. 930 Los Angeles, California 90017 |
| Anywhere | Wallet SDK and Commerce API | Coinbase Bermuda Technologies. Ltd. | 46 Reid Street, Hamilton HM12 Bermuda |
| Anywhere but the United States | Public and Private Node Staking | Coinbase Developer Platform Pte. Ltd. | One Marina Boulevard,  #28-00018989, Singapore |
| United States | Public and Private Node Staking | Coinbase Crypto Services, LLC | 1209 Orange Street, Corporation Trust Center  City of Wilmington, DE 19801 |

INSTITUTIONAL SERVICES

󰀐

For institutional entities or private clients receiving institutional services (such as Prime Trading & Custody and Prime DMA), the data controller is the entity with which you have contracted for the  products offered. Please refer to the terms of service or reach out to our Data Protection Officer at dpo@coinbase.com.
